List<Map<String, dynamic>> ECGPartTwoQuestions = [
  {
    'question':
        'Which condition is characterized by an irregularly irregular rhythm with no discernible P waves and an irregular ventricular response?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
      'Atrial flutter.',
      'Ventricular tachycardia.',
      'Supraventricular tachycardia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the primary purpose of the Q wave on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial depolarization.',
      'Ventricular depolarization.',
      'Atrial repolarization.',
      'Ventricular repolarization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which coronary artery supplies the inferior wall of the heart?',
    'answers': [
      'Left anterior descending (LAD).',
      'Left circumflex.',
      'Right coronary artery (RCA).',
      'Posterior descending artery (PDA).',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient presents with ST-segment elevation in leads II, III, and aVF. Which coronary artery is likely occluded?',
    'answers': [
      'Left anterior descending (LAD).',
      'Left circumflex.',
      'Right coronary artery (RCA).',
      'Left main coronary artery.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which ECG lead is best for detecting myocardial infarctions in the lateral wall of the heart?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V6.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the hallmark ECG finding in hyperkalemia?',
    'answers': [
      'Tall and peaked T waves.',
      'Widened QRS complexes.',
      'Prolonged PR intervals.',
      'ST-segment depression.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient presents with a regular rhythm, a heart rate of 180 bpm, and no visible P waves. What is the likely diagnosis?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
      'Ventricular tachycardia.',
      'Supraventricular tachycardia.',
      'Atrial flutter.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which lead on a 12-lead ECG is positioned at the fourth intercostal space just right of the sternum?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V3.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What does the J-point represent on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'The end of atrial depolarization.',
      'The beginning of ventricular repolarization.',
      'The junction between QRS complex and T wave.',
      'The point of maximum ventricular depolarization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient presents with a heart rate of 220 bpm, no P waves, and wide QRS complexes. What is the likely diagnosis?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
      'Ventricular tachycardia.',
      'Supraventricular tachycardia.',
      'Atrial flutter.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the significance of the PR segment on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'It represents atrial depolarization.',
      'It represents ventricular depolarization.',
      'It represents the isoelectric line between atrial and ventricular activity.',
      'It represents ventricular repolarization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which ECG lead is often used to diagnose right atrial enlargement?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V6.',],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'In which lead is the R wave typically smallest?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V6.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the primary purpose of the QRS complex on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial depolarization.',
      'Ventricular depolarization.',
      'Atrial repolarization.',
      'Ventricular repolarization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which arrhythmia is characterized by a wide QRS complex and no discernible P waves?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
      'Atrial flutter.',
      'Ventricular tachycardia.',
      'Supraventricular tachycardia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which electrolyte imbalance is associated with a prolonged PR interval and flattened P waves on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Hyperkalemia.',
      'Hypokalemia.',
      'Hypercalcemia.',
      'Hypocalcemia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient presents with ST-segment depression in leads V1-V4. Which coronary artery is likely occluded?',
    'answers': [
      'Left anterior descending (LAD).',
      'Left circumflex.',
      'Right coronary artery (RCA).',
      'Left main coronary artery.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which ECG lead is often used to diagnose left atrial enlargement?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V6.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the normal duration of the PR segment on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      '0.04 - 0.12 seconds.',
      '0.06 - 0.12 seconds.',
      '0.12 - 0.20 seconds.',
      '0.20 - 0.40 seconds.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient presents with ST-segment elevation in leads V1-V4. Which coronary artery is likely occluded?',
    'answers': [
      'Left anterior descending (LAD).',
      'Left circumflex.',
      'Right coronary artery (RCA).',
      'Left main coronary artery.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which electrolyte imbalance is associated with a shortened QT interval on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Hypernatremia.',
      'Hypokalemia.',
      'Hypercalcemia.',
      'Hypocalcemia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the primary purpose of the T wave on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial depolarization.',
      'Ventricular depolarization.',
      'Atrial repolarization.',
      'Ventricular repolarization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which lead on a 12-lead ECG is positioned at the fifth intercostal space at the anterior axillary line?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V7.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'A patient presents with a heart rate of 220 bpm, no P waves, and narrow QRS complexes. What is the likely diagnosis?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
      'Ventricular tachycardia.',
      'Supraventricular tachycardia.',
      'Atrial flutter.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which lead on a 12-lead ECG is positioned at the fifth intercostal space at the midaxillary line?',
    'answers': ['Lead I.', 'Lead II.', 'Lead V1.', 'Lead V8.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which arrhythmia is characterized by a rapid, regular rhythm with narrow QRS complexes and inverted P waves?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
      'Atrial flutter.',
      'Ventricular tachycardia.',
      'Supraventricular tachycardia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the most common cause of ST-segment depression on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Myocardial infarction.',
      'Pericarditis.',
      'Bundle branch block.',
      'Atrial fibrillation.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which segment of the ECG represents ventricular depolarization?',
    'answers': ['P wave.', 'PR interval.', 'QRS complex.', 'T wave.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the primary purpose of the Q wave on an ECG?',
    'answers': [
      'Atrial depolarization.',
      'Ventricular depolarization.',
      'Atrial repolarization.',
      'Ventricular repolarization.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which coronary artery supplies the lateral wall of the heart?',
    'answers': [
      'Left anterior descending (LAD).',
      'Left circumflex.',
      'Right coronary artery (RCA).',
      'Posterior descending artery (PDA).',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
];
